Gerald R. Gill Papers MS170
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Research and subject files, 1942 -- 2007; MS170.006; 12.2 Linear Feet 9 full record cartons, 1 partial record carton, 1 partial oversize box
  - United States history, circa 2000; MS170.006.022.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Vance, Jim letter list, circa 1994 -- 1998; MS170.006.022.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Voting, 2001; MS170.006.022.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - William A. Hinton lecture, the Tobacco Tyranny:: A history of how the Tobacco Industry targets African Americans, 1995; MS170.006.022.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Wilson, John, 2001 -- 2002; MS170.006.022.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - World War II, 1942, 1995-2005; MS170.006.022.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - World War II, 1980-1995; MS170.006.022.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - World War II, circa 1980 -- 2007; MS170.006.022.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Yancey, Charles, 1999 -- 2000; MS170.006.022.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Zvobgo, Eddison, 2004; MS170.006.022.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Index cards, circa 1980 -- 2007; MS170.006.023.00001; 1 Box(es) (Box 23)
- Teaching materials, 1978 -- 2007; MS170.007; 24 Linear Feet 20 record cartons
  This series is arranged in three sub-series: 1. Tufts courses; 2. Other courses; and 3. Student papers and review copies. Tufts Courses and Other courses are both grouped by class and arranged alphabetically; within each class grouping, folders are ordered chronologically.
  Student papers and review copies are arranged in three sub-subseries: 1. Class papers; 2. Tufts theses, dissertations, and senior special projects; and 3. Grant proposals and review copies. The class papers are student assignments, often graded, written by students for classes taught by Gill. Tufts theses, dissertations and senior special projects are major student works, typically involving original research. The grant proposals and review copies were materials related to Gill's interests that were sent to him by third parties for review. Each sub-subseries is arranged alphabetically by title.
  This series contains materials relating to courses taught by Gill at Tufts and elsewhere. Materials include syllabi, class handouts and presentations, course readings, exams, and student papers.
  The list of courses at Tufts include: The African American in United States History to 1865; the African American in United States History since 1865; America in the 19th Century; America in the 20th Century; the American Homefront During World War II; the American South Since 1865; the Civil Rights Movement in America; Empires and Exchange; Film and History; Sports in American History; and various additional, unidentified courses.
  There is also a small body of materials from courses taught at other institutions from 1978 to 1983. These include: Introduction to Black History (Howard University, 1976); African American History Since 1865, Comparative Slave Systems, and History of Black America 1877 to Present (University of the District of Columbia, circa 1978); and the Civil War and Reconstruction (Amherst College, 1983).
  - Tufts courses, 1980 -- 2007; MS170.007.001; 10.3 Linear Feet 8 full record cartons, 1 partial record carton
    Tufts Courses are both grouped by class and arranged alphabetically; within each class grouping, folders are ordered chronologically.
    This series contains materials relating to courses taught by Gill at Tufts. Materials include syllabi, class handouts and presentations, course readings, exams, and student papers. List of courses at Tufts include: The African American in United States History to 1865; the African American in United States History since 1865; America in the 19th Century; America in the 20th Century; the American Homefront During World War II; the American South Since 1865; the Civil Rights Movement in America; Empires and Exchange; Film and History; Sports in American History; and various additional, unidentified courses.
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1980 -- Fall 1987; MS170.007.001.024.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, 1981 -- 1982; MS170.007.001.024.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1981 -- Fall 1992; MS170.007.001.024.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, circa 1981 -- 2006; MS170.007.001.024.00004; 2 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, 1982 -- 1987; MS170.007.001.024.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1987; MS170.007.001.024.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, 1987 -- 1992; MS170.007.001.024.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, HST 95, 1987 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.024.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1988; MS170.007.001.024.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, HST 95, Fall 1988 -- Fall 2002; MS170.007.001.024.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1991; MS170.007.001.024.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1992; MS170.007.001.024.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, HST 95, 1992 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.024.00013; 2 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1993; MS170.007.001.024.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1993 -- Fall 2003; MS170.007.001.024.00015; 2 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 17-18)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1994; MS170.007.001.024.00016; 2 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1995 -- 1998; MS170.007.001.024.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1996; MS170.007.001.024.00018; 2 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 21-22)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1998; MS170.007.001.024.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1999; MS170.007.001.024.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, 1999 -- 2003; MS170.007.001.024.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1999 -- Fall 2004; MS170.007.001.024.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 2000; MS170.007.001.024.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 2002; MS170.007.001.024.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 2003; MS170.007.001.024.00025; 2 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 29-30)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 2003 -- Fall 2004; MS170.007.001.024.00026; 2 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 31-32)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 2004; MS170.007.001.025.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 2006; MS170.007.001.025.00002; 2 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, 1983 -- 1989; MS170.007.001.025.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, HST 96, circa 1983 -- 2007; MS170.007.001.025.00004; 3 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 6-8)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, Fall 1984; MS170.007.001.025.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, HST 96, 1985 -- 1995; MS170.007.001.025.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, Spring 1987; MS170.007.001.025.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, 1988 -- 1989; MS170.007.001.025.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 92A, Fall 1989; MS170.007.001.025.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, Spring 1990 -- Spring 1992; MS170.007.001.025.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 1990 -- Spring 2001; MS170.007.001.025.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, 1993 -- 2001; MS170.007.001.025.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 1993 -- Spring 2004; MS170.007.001.025.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, circa 1994; MS170.007.001.025.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 1995; MS170.007.001.025.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, 1995 -- 2001; MS170.007.001.025.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, 1995 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.025.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 1996; MS170.007.001.025.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, 1996 -- 2002; MS170.007.001.025.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 1997; MS170.007.001.025.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 1999; MS170.007.001.025.00021; 3 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 25-27)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 1999 -- Spring 2000; MS170.007.001.025.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2000; MS170.007.001.025.00023; 2 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 29-30)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, HST 172, Spring 2001; MS170.007.001.025.00024; 4 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 31-34)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 172, 2001 -- 2003; MS170.007.001.025.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2001 -- Spring 2005; MS170.007.001.025.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2004; MS170.007.001.025.00027; 2 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 37-38)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Fall 2004; MS170.007.001.025.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2004 -- Spring 2005; MS170.007.001.026.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2005; MS170.007.001.026.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 171, Fall 2005; MS170.007.001.026.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, 2005 -- 2006; MS170.007.001.026.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2006; MS170.007.001.026.00005; 3 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2006 -- Spring 2007; MS170.007.001.026.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 96, Spring 2007; MS170.007.001.026.00007; 2 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
    - America in the Nineteenth Century, HST 53, circa 1981 -- 1987; MS170.007.001.026.00008; 2 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, 1982 -- 1992; MS170.007.001.026.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, 1982 -- 1994; MS170.007.001.026.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, 1984 -- 1993; MS170.007.001.026.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, 1985 -- 1994; MS170.007.001.026.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, HST 87, Spring 1987; MS170.007.001.026.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, Spring 1988; MS170.007.001.026.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, HST 87, 1988 -- 1999; MS170.007.001.026.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, HST 87, Summer 1990 -- Spring 1994; MS170.007.001.026.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, Summer 1991; MS170.007.001.026.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, HST 87, 1992 -- 1994; MS170.007.001.026.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, Summer 1992 -- 1997; MS170.007.001.026.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, 87, Spring 1993; MS170.007.001.026.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 54, Summer 1993; MS170.007.001.026.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 87, 1993 -- 1997; MS170.007.001.026.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 87, 1994 -- 1997; MS170.007.001.026.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 87, Spring 1996; MS170.007.001.026.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 87, Spring 1997; MS170.007.001.026.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 87, 1997 -- 1999; MS170.007.001.026.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - America in the Twentieth Century, HST 87, Spring 1999; MS170.007.001.026.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - The American Homefront During World War II, HST 187 GG, circa 1988 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.027.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - The American Homefront During World War II, HST 187 GG, Fall 2000; MS170.007.001.027.00002; 2 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
    - The American Homefront During World War II, HST 187 GG, Fall 2000 -- Fall 2003; MS170.007.001.027.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - The American Homefront During World War II, HST 187 GG, 2000 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.027.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - The American Homefront During World War II, HST 187 GG, Fall 2004; MS170.007.001.027.00005; 2 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
    - The American South, 1880--1980, HST 191S, Fall 1984; MS170.007.001.027.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 002-GG, circa 1984 -- 1994; MS170.007.001.027.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 115, Fall 1987; MS170.007.001.027.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 002-GG, 1989 -- 1995; MS170.007.001.027.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 002-GG, 1988 -- 2003; MS170.007.001.027.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 002-GG, 1994 -- 2003; MS170.007.001.027.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 171, Fall 1995; MS170.007.001.027.00012; 2 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 15-16)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 171, circa 1995 -- 2005; MS170.007.001.027.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 002-GG, Fall 1999; MS170.007.001.027.00014; 3 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 18-20)
    - The Civil Rights Movement in America, 1930s to Present, HST 187A, Summer 2004; MS170.007.001.028.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - The Civil Rights Movement in America, 1930s to Present, HST 173, Summer 2006; MS170.007.001.028.00002; 2 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - The Civil Rights Movement in America, 1930s to Present, HST 187GG, Fall 2006; MS170.007.001.028.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Empires and Exchange, HST 8, Fall 1982; MS170.007.001.028.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Film and History, HST 202, Fall 1996; MS170.007.001.028.00005; 2 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
    - Film and History, HST 202, Spring 2005; MS170.007.001.028.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, circa 1997 -- 2007; MS170.007.001.028.00007; 3 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 10-12)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, 1997 -- 1998; MS170.007.001.028.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, 1997 -- 1999; MS170.007.001.028.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Summer 1997 -- Summer 2000; MS170.007.001.028.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, circa 1999; MS170.007.001.028.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Summer 2000; MS170.007.001.028.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, circa 2001; MS170.007.001.028.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Spring 2001; MS170.007.001.028.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, circa 2001 -- 2007; MS170.007.001.029.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Spring 2002; MS170.007.001.029.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, 2002 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.029.00003; 2 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Spring 2003; MS170.007.001.029.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Spring 2004; MS170.007.001.029.00005; 4 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Fall 2004; MS170.007.001.029.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, 2004 -- 2007; MS170.007.001.029.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Spring 2005; MS170.007.001.029.00008; 3 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 10-12)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Spring 2006; MS170.007.001.029.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Summer 2007; MS170.007.001.029.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Various courses, circa 1983 -- 2006; MS170.007.001.029.00011; 3 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 15-17)
    - Various courses, Spring 1983 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.029.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Various courses, 1984 -- 2004; MS170.007.001.029.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Various courses, 1988; MS170.007.001.029.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Various courses, 1989 -- 2001; MS170.007.001.029.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 001-GG, Fall 2003; MS170.007.001.030.00001; 3 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 172, 2003 -- 2005; MS170.007.001.030.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - The American South Since 1865, HST 172, Fall 2005; MS170.007.001.030.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Civil rights movement course, 1981 -- 2006; MS170.007.001.030.00004; 2 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
    - Seminar on the Civil Rights Movement, HST 93B, Spring 1981; MS170.007.001.030.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Seminar on the Civil Rights Movement, C101/C201, Fall 1986; MS170.007.001.030.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Seminar on the Civil Rights Movement, World War II to the Present, 93C, 1986 -- 1987; MS170.007.001.030.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, World War II to the Present, 93C, Spring 1987; MS170.007.001.030.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, World War II to the Present, 192A, Spring 1989; MS170.007.001.030.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, World War II to the Present, 192A, Spring 1990; MS170.007.001.030.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, World War II to the Present, 192A, Summer 1992 -- 1997; MS170.007.001.030.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, World War II to the Present, 187, Fall 1993; MS170.007.001.030.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, World War II to the Present, 187A, Summer 1994; MS170.007.001.030.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, 1935--Present, 187GG, Fall 1996; MS170.007.001.030.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - The Civil Rights Movement in America, 187GG, circa 1996 -- 2002; MS170.007.001.030.00015; 4 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 18-21)
    - The Civil Rights Movement in America, 187GG, Fall 1998; MS170.007.001.030.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - "The Life and Times of Paul Robeson" documentary teaching guide, 1998; MS170.007.001.030.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - The Civil Rights Movement, 1935--Present, 187GG, Fall 2002; MS170.007.001.030.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - The Civil Rights Movement in America, 1935--Present, 187GG, Summer 2004; MS170.007.001.030.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, Summer 1999; MS170.007.001.031.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Sports in American History, HST 172B, circa 1997 -- 2007; MS170.007.001.031.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - The Civil Rights Movement in America, HST 187, Summer 2003; MS170.007.001.031.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1989; MS170.007.001.031.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 57, Fall 1987; MS170.007.001.031.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, Fall 1994; MS170.007.001.031.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - The African American in United States History to 1865, HST 95, 2003 -- 2006; MS170.007.001.031.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - The African American in United States History Since 1865, HST 58, 1981 -- 1993; MS170.007.001.031.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 5)